ILGWU Health and Safety Department Records 5780/208
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILGWU Health and Safety Department Records
1953-1998
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU)
5780/208
16 cubic feet
16 linear ft.
Records (documents).
The collection contains company files, training files, and subject files that include information on workplace hazards, standards and studies, and other health and safety programs.
6791853
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 05, 2011
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 16, 2019
Biographical / Historical
The International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union was once one of the largest labor unions in the United States founded in 1900 by local union delegates representing about 2,000 members in cities in the northeastern United States. It was one of the first U.S. Unions to have a membership consisting of mostly females, and it played a key role in the labor history of the 1920s and 1930s. The union is generally referred to as the "ILGWU" or the "ILG". The ILGWU grew in geographical scope, membership size, and political influence to become one of the most powerful forces in American organized labor by mid-century. Representing workers in the women's garment industry, the ILGWU worked to improve working and living conditions of its members through collective bargaining agreements, training programs, health care facilities, cooperative housing, educational opportunities, and other efforts. The ILGWU merged with the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union in 1995 to form the Union of Needle trades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE). UNITE merged with the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE) in 2004 to create a new union known as UNITE HERE. The two unions that formed UNITE in 1995 represented only 250,000 workers between them, down from the ILGWU's peak membership of 450,000 in 1969.
Biographical / Historical
The Health and Safety Department was established in 1980 by the ILGWU to research health and safety hazards in the workplace, lead training programs on occupational safety for members as well as unorganized workers, and provide technical assistance relating to workplace safety. With partial financial support from the Department of Labor, Occupational Safety and Health Administration, the Health and Safety Department offered programming to ILGWU regions, locals, and affiliates, as well as for unorganized workers in the garment industry.
Scope and Contents
Arranged alphabetically by name, the company files document the Health and Safety Department's participation in the investigation and improvement of conditions in workplaces around the country, including correspondence, memoranda, and reports on shops. The Health and Safety Department also maintains several subseries of subject files: one was on workplace hazards; these are arranged alphabetically by industry. A second was a general subject file that included topics relating to the routine business and research of the department; these are arranged alphabetically by topic. The third is constituted of the health and safety organizations of other unions, as well as unions outside of the United States. The final series contains training materials, including files pertaining to specific trainings, files of handouts on specific workplace hazards, and files of graphics and originals used in the production of the department's training materials and publications.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5780: ILGWU records
Laundry workers--Labor unions; Textile workers--Labor unions; Clothing workers--Labor unions; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union.; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union --Archives; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Health and Safety Dept.--Archives; Laundry, Dry Cleaning, and Dye House Workers International Union --Archives; Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees --Archives; UNITE HERE (Organization) --Archives
6791853
- Ace Plastics Brooklyn, New York, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- A&K Knitting Farmingdale, New York, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Alle Processing Brooklyn, New York, 1988-1993 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Alle Processing Brooklyn, New York, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Ames INC., 1992 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Anne Klein- Local 10 (Project), 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Anne Klein-Local 10 (Project), 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Anne Klein- Local 10 (Project), 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Scope and Contents
  Confidential (medical); work and health questionnaires
- Apex Paper Box Company Cleveland, Ohio, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Archer Rubber Milford, Massachusetts, 1987-1994 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Archer Rubber Milford, Massachusetts, 1987-1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Archer Rubber Milford, Massachusetts, 1987-1994 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Archer Rubber Milford, Massachusetts, Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA) Files, 1987-1993 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Archer Rubber Milford, Massachusetts, Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA) Files, 1987-1993 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Archer Rubber Milford, Massachusetts, DOSH Files, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- A& S Speedmark, Secaucus, New Jersey, 1989-1992 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Avant Modes, Bronx, New York, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Avon Home Fashions. Boston, Massachusetts, 1992-1994 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Barsew Atlantic Apparel, Lehighton. Pennsylvania, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Bay State Curtain, Fitchburg, Massachusetts, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Bay State Smelting, Somerville, Massachusetts, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Bay State Smelting, Somerville, Massachusetts, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Bay State Smelting, Somerville, Massachusetts, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Bennington Pottery, Bennington, Vermont, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Bennington Pottery, Bennington, Vermont, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  Photos and Negatives
- Bergdorf Goodman, New York, New York, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Brentwood Optical Company, Jersey City, New Jersey, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Bridgeton Knitting Mill, Bridgeton, Maine, 1991-1995 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Bridgeton Knitting Mill, Bridgeton, Maine, 1991-1995 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Bridgeton Knitting Mills, Bridgeton, Maine, worker health surveys, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  confidential
- Bridgeton Knitting Mills, Bridgeton, Maine, worker health surveys, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Bridgeton Knitting Mills, Bridgeton, Maine, worker health surveys, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- BTF Corporation, East Rutherford, New Jersey, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Butler MacDonald, Montgomeryville, Pennsylvania, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Calvin Klein, New York, New York, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Camden Tannery, Camden, Maine, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Camden Tannery, Camden, Maine, Company Information, 1953-1985 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Camden Tannery, Camden, Maine, Clippings, 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Camden Tannery, Camden, Maine, 1986-1988 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Camden Tannery, Camden, Maine, 1986-1988 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Camden Tannery, Camden, Maine, Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA) Chemical Lists, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Camden Tannery, Camden, Maine, Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA), 1973-1992 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Camden Tannery, Camden, Maine, Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA), 1973-1992 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Camden Tannery, Camden, Maine, Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA), 1973-1992 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Camden Tannery, Camden, Maine, 1985-1988 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Camden Tannery, Camden, Maine, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Camden Tannery, Camden, Maine, Meeting attendance, 1983-1986 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Camden Tannery, Camden, Maine, data for union, 1983-1989 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Camden Tannery, Camden, Maine, data for union, 1983-1989 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Camden Tannery, Camden, Maine, 1986-1988 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Camden Tannery, Camden, Maine, Labor-Management Reporting and Disclosure Act, 1953-1988 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Camden Tannery, Camden, Maine, Material Safety Data Sheets, 1984-1988 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Camden Tannery, Camden, Maine, Material Safety Data Sheets, 1984-1988 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Camden Tannery, Camden, Maine, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  confidential; health and safety surveys
- Chemi-Coating, Walden, New York, 1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Columbia Tanning, Brockton, Massachusetts, 1989-1994 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Chadwick/Hit or Miss, Boston Massachusetts`, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Liz Claiborne, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Codman Company, Rockland, Massachusetts, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Continental extrusion, fire training (Box 2, Folder 31)
  no date
- Dauman Recycling, Carteret, New Jersey, 1991-1993 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Dauman Recycling, Carteret, New Jersey, 1991-1993 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  SSNS
- Debbie Sue, Bethlehem, Pennsylvania, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- DeMoulin Brothers, Greenville, Illinois, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  medical
- DeMoulin Brothers, Greenville, Illinois, safety surveys (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Domsey, Brooklyn, New York, organizing, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Dynamic Plastics, East Elmhurst, New York, 1988-1990 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Eastland Woolen Mill, Corinna, Maine, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Eastland Woolen Mill, Corinna, Maine, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Eastland Woolen Mill, Corinna, Maine, anonymous, health and safety questionnaire, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  SSNS; medical
- Emsig Manufacturing, safety policy, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Emsig Manufacturing, Hudson, New York, 1990-1994 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Emsig Manufacturing, Hudson, New York, 1990-1994 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Emsig Manufacturing, Hudson, New York, 1990-1994 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Emsig Manufacturing, Hudson, New York, 1990-1994 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Emsig Manufacturing, Villas, New Jersey, 1991-1994 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Emsig Manufacturing, Villas, New Jersey, 1991-1994 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Emsig Manufacturing, Villas, New Jersey, 1991-1994 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Emsig Manufacturing, Villas, New Jersey, Rodriguez, Carlos, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Emsig Manufacturing, Villas, New Jersey, Rodriguez, Carlos, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Enbee Plastics, New York, New York, 1991-1994 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Evan Picone, North Bergen, New Jersey, 1983-1991 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Futuramik, Hartford, Connecticut, 1991-1995 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Futuramik, Hartford, Connecticut, 1991-1995 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Futuramik, Hartford, Connecticut, 1991-1995 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Futuramik, Hartford, Connecticut, 1991-1995 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Futuramik, Hartford, Connecticut, 1991-1995 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Futuramik, Hartford, Connecticut, 1991-1995 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Gary Plastics, Bronx, New York, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Gelberg Braid/Tamber Kuits, New York, New York, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- D. Glasgow and Sons, Perth Amboy, New Jersey, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Great American Products, Chicago, Illinois, 1992-1994 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Hartford Faience, Hartford, Connecticut, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Louis Hornick and Company, Local 155, Haverstraw, New York, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Louis Hornick and Company, Local 155, Haverstraw, New York, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Hygiene Industries, Sardis, Mississippi, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Hygiene Industries, Vienna, Ohio, citation, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Hygiene Industries, Vienna, Ohio, citation, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Hygiene Industries, Vienna, Ohio, clippings, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Hygiene Industries, Vienna, Ohio, 1989-1992 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Hygiene Industries, Vienna, Ohio, 1989-1992 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Hygiene Industries, Vienna, Ohio, 1989-1992 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Hygiene Industries, Vienna, Ohio, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Hygiene Industries, Vienna, Ohio, chemical, fire hazards, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Isratex, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- J.C. and Me, Holsople, Pennsylvania, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Jena Bridal, New York, New York, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- J.H. Collectibles, Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 1991-1995 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- J.H. Collectibles, Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 1991-1995 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- J.H. Collectibles, Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 1991-1995 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Kids-R-US, organizing, warehouse, New Jersey, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  health and safety questionnaires
- K-Mart, Groveport, Ohio, 1990-1993 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- K-Mart, Groveport, Ohio, 1990-1993 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Koret, San Francisco, California, 1993-1995 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Lechters, INC., Harrison, New Jersey, Guillen, Jose, 1991-1994 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Leslie Fay, 1991-1994 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Leslie Fay, 1991-1994 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Leslie Fay, 1991-1994 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Leslie Fay, 1991-1994 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Leslie Fay, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  confidential; symptoms survey
- Leslie Fay, medical, White, Connie, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Leslie Fay, Wilkes-Barre, Pennsylvania, 1991-1994 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Leslie Fay, Wilkes-Barre, Pennsylvania, 1991-1994 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Leslie Fay, Wilkes-Barre, Pennsylvania, 1991-1994 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Leslie Fay, Wilkes-Barre, Pennsylvania, 1992-1994 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  medical documents
- Mademoiselle, 1992-1997 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Mademoiselle, 1992-1997 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Made-Rite, New York, New York, 1990-1995 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Maidenform, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Maidenform, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Maidenform, 1988-1990 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Maidenform, 1988-1990 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Malden Mills, Lawrence, Massachusetts, Health and Safety Committee, 1989-1994 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Malden Mills, Lawrence, Massachusetts, Health and Safety Committee, 1989-1994 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Malden Mills, general, 1980-1996 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Malden Mills, general, 1980-1996 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Malden Mills, general, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Malden Mills, general, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Malden Mills, Glenn Street, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Malden Mills, Hudson Mills, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Malden Mills, Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA), 1993-1995 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Marcraft, Local 155, warehouse, Elmsford, New York, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Mariners-Astubeco, Edgewater, New Jersey, 1986-1994 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Mariners-Astubeco, Edgewater, New Jersey, 1986-1994 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Mariners-Astubeco, Edgewater, New Jersey, 1986-1994 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Marsh Allen, Cleveland, Ohio, organizing, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- MCF Industries, Drive, lead, degreasers, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Merry-Go-Round Enterprises, Maryland, 1988-1992 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Merry-Go-Round Enterprises, Maryland (Box 5, Folder 19)
  safety and health hazards in warehouses surveys; no date
- Merry-Go-Round Enterprises, Maryland (Box 5, Folder 20)
  safety and health hazards in warehouses survey; no date
- Metropolitan Fashion Council, Brooklyn, New York, 1991-1993 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Miss Elaine, Bristow, Oklahoma, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Monette Casuals, Avenal, New Jersey, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Monterey Mills, Wisconsin, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- M.S. Schmalburg, New York, New York, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Multicolor, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Nessor Alloy, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Paterson Laundry and Dye, Paterson, New Jersey, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Personality Handkerchiefs, Newark, New Jersey, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Plastonics, Hartford, Connecticut, 1992-1995 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Plastonics, Hartford, Connecticut, 1992-1995 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Plastonics, Hartford, Connecticut, 1992-1995 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Plastonics, Hartford, Connecticut, notes on walkthroughs and safety meetings, 1992-1995 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Plastonics, Hartford, Connecticut, notes on walkthroughs and safety meetings, 1992-1995 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Plastonics, Hartford, Connecticut, Plastonics News and Organize, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Plastonics, Hartford, Connecticut, Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA) citations, complaints, Department of Environmental Protection (DEP) complaint, 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Princeton Hosiery Mill, Princeton, Kentucky, organizing, 1987-1989 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Pymm Thermometer Corporation, Brooklyn, New York, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Pymm Thermometer Corporation, Brooklyn, New York, news, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Pymm Thermometer Corporation, Brooklyn, New York, Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA) Citations, 1981-1986 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Pymm Thermometer Corporation, Brooklyn, New York, Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA), New York Department of Health (DOH) and Division of Industrial Hygiene (DOIH) Records, 1971-1985 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Pymm Thermometer Corporation, Brooklyn, New York, Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA), New York Department of Health (DOH) and Division of Industrial Hygiene (DOIH) Records, 1971-1985 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Pymm Thermometer Corporation, Brooklyn, New York, Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA), New York Department of Health (DOH) and Division of Industrial Hygiene (DOIH) Records, 1971-1985 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Pymm Thermometer Corporation, Brooklyn, New York, worker tests, general information, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Rainfare (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Recycling Consulting Group, West Haven, Connecticut, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Regal Originals, New York, New York, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Ridge Printing, Ridgefield, New Jersey, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Robinson Manufacturing, Oxford, Maine, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Roxanne, Neptune, New Jersey, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Revelation Bra Company, Boston, Massachusetts, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- RussTogs, Long Island City, New York, medical surveys, September 8, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- RussTogs, Long Island City, New York, 1989-1991 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- RussTogs, Long Island City, New York, 1985-1990 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- RussTogs, Long Island City, New York, 1985-1990 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Sawyers of Napa, California, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Scotty's Fashions/Kresgeville Manufacturing, Kresgeville, Pennsylvania, 1989-1993 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Shore Plastics, Freeport, New York, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Shumsky, New York, New York, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Shumsky, New York, New York, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Shumsky, New York, New York, 1991-1993 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  medical records
- Shumsky, New York, New York, 1991-1993 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Shumsky, New York, New York, lead problems, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Shumsky, New York, New York, lead problems, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- S.K. Plastics, Brooklyn, New York, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Smoler Brothers, Herrin, Illinois, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Tama Manufacturing, Northampton, Pennsylvania, 1992-1994 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Uretek, New Haven, Connecticut, 1987-1994 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Uretek, New Haven, Connecticut, 1987-1994 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Uretek, New Haven, Connecticut, 1987-1994 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Uretek, New Haven, Connecticut, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Uretek, New Haven, Connecticut, clippings, 1987-1994 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Uretek, New Haven, Connecticut, contract, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Uretek, New Haven, Connecticut, International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU) Training, 1987-1990 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Uretek, New Haven, Connecticut, training material, 1987-1989 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Uretek, New Haven, Connecticut, Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA) citations, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Uretek, New Haven, Connecticut, testing and surveillance program, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Uretek, New Haven, Connecticut, worker's compensation, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Valerie Fashions, Wind gap, Pennsylvania, 1982-1998 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Vanguard Military Equipment, Long Island City, New York, 1991-1993 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Vinylaire Windows, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- West Helena Sportswear, West Helena, Arkansas, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Wirt Inflatables Specialists, Elizabeth, West Virginia, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Woolrich Mills, Woolrich, Pennsylvania, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Woolrich Mills, Woolrich, Pennsylvania, organizing, 1981-1988 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Woolrich Mills, Woolrich, Pennsylvania, organizing, 1981-1988 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Garment Industry hazards, fact sheets, 1980-1994 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- new technology in the garment industry, 1986-1995 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- new technology in the garment industry, 1986-1995 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- new technology in the garment industry, 1986-1995 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- General health and safety, 1972-1981 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Hairdressers, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- High tech, 1981-1987 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- High tech, 1981-1987 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- High tech, 1981-1987 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Leather, belts, Material Safety Data Sheets and information, 1976-1995 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Meatpacking industry, 1984-1992 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Meatpacking industry, 1984-1992 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous industries, 1976-1991 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Plastics, 1972-1991 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Plastics, 1972-1991 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Plastics, 1972-1991 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Rubber workers, 1980-1990 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Screen-printing, 1978-1985 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Shipyard safety, 1980-1995 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Warehouses, 1978-1992 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Warehouses, 1978-1992 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Warehouses, 1978-1992 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Warehouses, 1978-1992 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Forklifts, 1978-1991 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Forklifts, 1978-1991 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Forklifts, 1978-1991 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Access Standard, 1983-1988 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  Access to employee exposure and medical records
- Access Standard, administrative activity, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Access Standard, information fact sheets, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Access Standard, National Labor Relations Board (NLRB) decisions, 1979-1982 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Access Standard. Sample letters and leaflets (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Air Containment Standard, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Asbestos Standard, 1986-1991 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Blood borne pathogens standard, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Emergency Temporary Standard, petition, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Epidemiological studies, spontaneous abortions research, 1978-1982 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Epidemiological studies, epidemiology, 1979-1989 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Epidemiological studies, Harvard, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Epidemiological studies, Harvard, McCunney, formaldehyde, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Epidemiological studies, job stress, heart disease, National Institute of Occupational Safety and Health (NIOSH) study, 1981-1983 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Epidemiological studies, Harvard, musculo-skeletal, Prunett/Keyserling, 1978-1982 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Epidemiological studies, National Cancer Institute, environmental, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Epidemiological studies, National Institute of Occupational Safety and Health (NIOSH) research studies, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Epidemiological studies, occupational disease in California, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Epidemiological studies, occupational physician Goldman, Rose, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Epidemiological studies, occupational studies, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Epidemiological studies, soft tissue disorders of upper limbs of women garment workers, Purnett, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 21)